<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">Physician-patients often give unwarranted or unhelpful recommendations or advice regarding their own care.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Physician-patients often arrive in the late stages of their disease.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Physician-patients require less explanation than non-physician patients in the discussion of their diagnosis.</statement>
     <statement id="4">Physician-patients often like to get technical with discussions of treatment options.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Physician-patients have an educated opinion on their treatment options.</statement>
     <statement id="6">Physician-patients have more realistic expectations of their disease process.</statement>
     <statement id="7">Physician-patients seem to have more internal drive to recover.</statement>
     <statement id="8">Physician-patients have better participation in their own care.</statement>
     <statement id="9">Physician-patients more often exhibit hypochondriac tendencies.</statement>
     <statement id="10">Physician-patients often self-diagnose before coming in, and this annoys me.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Physician-patients are more likely to demonstrate anxiety or helplessness than other patients.</statement>
     <statement id="12">Physician-patients are more likely to exhibit anger or reactance against their condition than other patients.</statement>
     <statement id="13">Physician-patients have simpler cases of disease.</statement>
     <statement id="14">Physician-patients allow me to examine them more closely.</statement>
     <statement id="15">Physician-patients are more demanding than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="16">Consults or appointments with physician-patients take less time than with non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="17">Physician-patients consume fewer resources than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="18">Physician-patients require fewer visits and less follow-up than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="19">Physician-patients are often more grateful and reasonable than the average patient.</statement>
     <statement id="20">Physician-patients skip routine screening with greater frequency than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="21">Physician-patients are more adherent with follow-up and preventative medicine.</statement>
     <statement id="22">Physician-patients are less likely to present with trivial cases of disease.</statement>
     <statement id="23">Physician-patients have a better sense of humor about their condition.</statement>
     <statement id="24">Physician-patients are more enjoyable to treat.</statement>
     <statement id="25">Physician-patients cope with their conditions better.</statement>
     <statement id="26">I feel more pressured when treating patients who are physicians.</statement>
     <statement id="27">Physician-patients are more honest and truthful with me than other patients.</statement>
     <statement id="28">Physician-patients are more likely to communicate with me outside of consultations.</statement>
     <statement id="29">Family of physician-patients are easier to work with, and have more faith in my recommendations.</statement>
     <statement id="30">I feel I heal faster, or recover quicker from illnesses than many of my patients.</statement>
     <statement id="31">Physicians treating me appear to use out-of-date evidence in my treatments.</statement>
     <statement id="32">When presenting as a patient to another physician, I feel pressured to be a "good" patient.</statement>
     <statement id="33">I wait longer in my disease course to present to my physician than the average patient.</statement>
     <statement id="34">I probably trouble my physicians less than their average patient.</statement>
     <statement id="35">I am afraid that the questions I ask as a physician-patient are sometimes poorly-received or come across as disrespectful.</statement>
   </statements>