<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">Physician-patients often give unwarranted or unhelpful recommendations or advice regarding their own care.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Consults or appointments with physician-patients take less time than with non-physician patients. </statement>
     <statement id="3">Physician-patients are more demanding than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="4">Physician-patients consume fewer resources than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Physician-patients require fewer visits and less follow-up than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="6">Physician-patients are often more grateful and reasonable than the average patient. </statement>
     <statement id="7">I feel more pressured when treating patients who are physicians.</statement>
     <statement id="8">When presenting as a patient to another physician, I feel pressured to be a "good" patient.</statement>
     <statement id="9">I feel I heal faster, or recover quicker from illnesses than many of my patients.</statement>
     <statement id="10">Physician-patients skip routine screening with greater frequency than non-physician patients.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Physicians treating me appear to use out-of-date evidence in my treatments.</statement>
     <statement id="12">Physician-patients often arrive in the late stages of their disease.</statement>
     <statement id="13">Physician-patients require less explanation than non-physician patients in the discussion of their diagnosis.</statement>
     <statement id="14">Physician-patients often like to get technical with discussions of treatment options.</statement>
     <statement id="15">Physician-patients have an educated opinion on their treatment options.</statement>
     <statement id="16">I probably trouble my physicians less than their average patient.</statement>
   </statements>